Mertz mss., 1902-2019 LMC 2914
Lilly Library
- Elizabeth Peters
  - Amelia Peabody Series
    - The Hippopotamus Pool
      - Second draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 18, Folder 18-20)
      - "Almost final revisions" - typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
      - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 19, Folder 5-8)
      - Plot outlines, notes, and research materials, 1995? (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Cover proofs and sketches, 1995? (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Reviews, publicity, publishing correspondence, and style sheets, 1995-1996; 2 Folders (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
      - "Quotes for Hippo", 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Cover mock-up, undated (Box 187)
    - Seeing a Large Cat
      - Second draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
      - Third draft - typescript (folders 1-3), undated; 3 Folders (Box 19, Folder 17-19)
      - Third draft - typescript (folder 4), 1960-2011 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - First pass galleys, 31 January 1997; 3 Folders (Box 20, Folder 2-4)
      - Final revision - annotated typescript, 3 December 1996; 4 Folders (Box 20, Folder 5-8)
      - Draft - annotated typescript, 30 December 1997; 4 Folders (Box 20, Folder 9-12)
      - Cover proofs and sketches, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Plot outlines, notes, research materials, and style sheet, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - The Ape Who Guards the Balance
      - Second draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 20, Folder 16-18)
      - Draft - annotated typescript (folders 1-2), undated; 2 Folders (Box 20, Folder 19-20)
      - Draft - annotated typescript (folders 3-4), undated; 2 Folders (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      - Foul matter, 11 November 1997; 4 Folders (Box 21, Folder 3-6)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 21, Folder 7-10)
      - Cover proofs, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Plot outlines, notes, and style sheets, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Publicity tour, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence (folders 1-4), undated; 4 Folders (Box 21, Folder 14-17)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence (folder 5), undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Promotional standee, undated (Box 188)
    - The Falcon at the Portal
      - Galley proofs, 4 January 1999; 3 Folders (Box 22, Folder 2-4)
      - First draft - typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Rough draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 22, Folder 6-8)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript, 12 November 1998; 5 Folders (Box 22, Folder 9-13)
      - Foul matter, 4 Folders (Box 22, Folder 14-17)
      - Cover proofs, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence (folder 1), 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence (folders 2-3), 1998-2000; 2 Folders (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
      - Annotated galleys, undated (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - He Shall Thunder in the Sky
      - Page proofs, undated; 2 Folders (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
      - Second draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 23, Folder 5-7)
      - Second pass - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
      - First draft - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
      - First pass - typescript, 18 January 2000; 3 Folders (Box 23, Folder 12-14)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript (folders 1-4), undated; 4 Folders (Box 23, Folder 15-18)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript (folder 5), undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Foul matter, 5 June 2000; 5 Folders (Box 24, Folder 2-6)
      - Style sheets, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Cover proofs, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 2000-2001; 5 Folders (Box 24, Folder 9-13)
      - Promotional standee, undated (Box 187)
    - Lord of the Silent
      - Third draft - annotated typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 24, Folder 14-17)
      - Second draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
      - Early draft - annotated typescript (folder 1), undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Early draft - annotated typescript (folders 2-3), undated; 2 Folders (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 25, Folder 3-6)
      - Galleys, 2000; 8 Folders (Box 25, Folder 7-14)
      - Notes and style sheets, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Article/introduction, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - "Sales and bestseller lists", 2001 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 2000-2001; 3 Folders (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
    - The Golden One
      - "Next to last version" - annotated typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 26, Folder 4-7)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
      - "Second or third draft" - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 26, Folder 10-12)
      - Foul matter, undated; 4 Folders (Box 26, Folder 13-16)
      - Draft - annotated typescript (folder 1), undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Draft - annotated typescript (folders 2-3), undated; 2 Folders (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
      - Cover proofs and sketch, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Bestseller lists, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 2001-2003; 3 Folders (Box 27, Folder 5-7)
      - Notes and style sheets, 2001? (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Promotional standee, 2002? (Box 187)
      - Cover mock-up, undated (Box 187)
    - Children of the Storm
      - Penultimate draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 27, Folder 9-11)
      - Revised galleys, 22 January 2003; 3 Folders (Box 27, Folder 12-14)
      - Audiobook script, undated; 3 Folders (Box 27, Folder 15-17)
      - Galleys (folders 1-2), 3 January 2003; 2 Folders (Box 27, Folder 18-19)
      - Galleys (folder 3), 3 January 2003 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Foul matter, 2003; 6 Folders (Box 28, Folder 2-7)
      - Draft - annotated typescript, 21 October 2002; 4 Folders (Box 28, Folder 8-11)
      - Draft - annotated typescript, 24 September 2001; 2 Folders (Box 28, Folder 12-13)
      - Cover proofs, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Sales and bestseller lists, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Notes and style sheet, 2002? (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence (folders 1-2), 2002-2003; 2 Folders (Box 28, Folder 17-18)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence (folders 3-4), 2002-2003; 2 Folders (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - Guardian of the Horizon
      - First pass - annotated typescript, 2 January 2004; 3 Folders (Box 29, Folder 3-5)
      - Author's galleys, 2 January 2004; 5 Folders (Box 29, Folder 6-10)
      - "Next to last version" - annotated typescript, 4 November 2004; 3 Folders (Box 29, Folder 11-13)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 29, Folder 14-17)
      - Foul matter (folder 1), 20 July 2004 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Foul matter (folders 2-4), 20 July 2004; 3 Folders (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 2004-2005; 2 Folders (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
      - Cover proofs and sketches, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Notes, plot outline, and research materials, 2002-2003? (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Sales and bestseller lists, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Cover mock-ups, undated (Box 187)
      - Framed cover and bestseller list (Box 182)
    - The Serpent on the Crown
      - Incomplete draft - typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Rough draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 30, Folder 10-12)
      - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 30, Folder 13-15)
      - Page proofs, 14 February 2005; 2 Folders (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
      - Foul matter (folders 1-2), 2004; 2 Folders (Box 30, Folder 18-19)
      - Foul matter (folders 3-10), 2004; 8 Folders (Box 31, Folder 1-8)
      - Cover proofs, 2005? (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 2005; 2 Folders (Box 31, Folder 10-11)
      - Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Penultimate draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 31, Folder 13-15)
      - Three gold promotional chocolate pyramids (chocolate removed) (Box 144)
    - Tomb of the Golden Bird
      - First pass - annotated typescript, 19 December 2005; 3 Folders (Box 31, Folder 16-18)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript (folder 1), undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript (folders 2-4), undated; 3 Folders (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
      - Draft - annotated typescript, 22 November 2005; 4 Folders (Box 32, Folder 4-7)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 32, Folder 8-11)
      - Draft - typescript, undated; 4 Folders (Box 32, Folder 12-15)
      - Foul matter (folders 1-2), 4 January 2007; 2 Folders (Box 32, Folder 16-17)
      - Foul matter (folder 3), 4 January 2007 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Revised and third pass - typescript, 9 January 2006; 3 Folders (Box 33, Folder 2-4)
      - Cover proofs and sketches, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Notes and style sheets, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 2006-2007; 2 Folders (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
      - Second pass - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 191, Folders 8-10)
    - A River in the Sky
      - First pass - annotated typescript, 13 October 2009; 2 Folders (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
      - Foul matter, 2009; 3 Folders (Box 33, Folder 11-13)
      - Revised and third pass - typescript, 24 November 2009; 2 Folders (Box 33, Folder 14-15)
      - Revised draft - typescript, 28 October 2009; 2 Folders (Box 33, Folder 16-17)
      - Endpaper maps and design layouts, 2009-2010 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Cover proofs, 2010? (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Bestseller lists and sales, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 2009-2011; 2 Folders (Box 33, Folder 21-22)
      - Second draft - typescript, undated; 5 Folders (Box 190, Folders 1-5)
    - The Painted Queen
      - First pass - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
      - "Interim Hess draft", undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Chapter one, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Chapter two, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Chapter three, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Chapter five, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Notes and research materials, 2010-2011? (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Cover proofs, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Publicity, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Framed cover and bestseller list (Box 182)
      - Promotional standee (Box 186)
    - Amelia Peabody's Egypt
      - "Compendium errors/corrections/changes", 2004? (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Reviews, publicity, and publishing correspondence, 2003; 2 Folders (Box 34, Folder 12-13)
      - Bound proofs, 2003; 3 Folders (Box 34, Folder 14-16)
      - Cover proofs, undated (Box 187)
      - "Egypt reference material" (oversize) (Box 189)
      - "Photos for compendium", 1902-2019 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - "Amelia 1912-1914 - weapons, etc", 1999? (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - "Repackage", 2010-2011 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - "Amelia - characters", undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - "Miscellaneous plot ideas and genealogy", 1994-1997? (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - "Another Shirt Ruined" website, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Interviews, 1992? (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Untitled story - typescript, undated (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - Amelia Peabody paper dolls, undated (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Unknown cover proof, undated (Box 197)
  - Possible titles, undated (Box 191, Folder 23)
- Barbara Michaels
  - Georgetown Trilogy
    - Ammie, Come Home
      - Master proofs (folder 1), 17 July 1968 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Master proofs (folder 2), 17 July 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Final draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
      - First draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
      - Revised draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
      - Serialisations and condensed versions, 1968-1969 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Plot outlines and notes, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Cover proofs, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1969? (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Woman's Own - Ammie Come Home serialization, 1969 (Box 187)
    - Shattered Silk
      - Second draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 35, Folder 12-14)
      - First draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 35, Folder 15-17)
      - Page proofs (folders 1-2), undated; 2 Folders (Box 35, Folder 18-19)
      - Page proofs (folder 3), undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Author's proofs, undated; 3 Folders (Box 36, Folder 2-4)
      - Setter's proof, undated; 3 Folders (Box 36, Folder 5-7)
      - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 36, Folder 8-10)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Good Housekeeping - serialization, August 1986 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Stitches in Time
      - Master galleys, 6 March 1995; 2 Folders (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
      - Second pass - annotated typescript, 15 February 1995; 2 Folders (Box 36, Folder 14-15)
      - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 36, Folder 16-18)
      - Copyedited draft - annotated typescript, 6 January 1995; 2 Folders (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
      - Draft - typescript, 16 January 1995; 2 Folders (Box 37, Folder 3-4)
      - Draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 37, Folder 5-7)
      - Draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 37, Folder 8-10)
      - Abridged audiobook script, 27 January 1995 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Corrected page proofs, 23 February 1995 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1995-1998 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Cover proof, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Notes, plot outlines, and research materials, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Someone in the House Series
    - Black Rainbow
      - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 37, Folder 16-18)
      - Revised draft, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Notes and plot outline, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Cover proof, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Someone in the House
      - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
      - Revised draft - typescript, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1981-1989? (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Cover proofs, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Plot outlines, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Cosmopolitan - serialization, 1982 (Box 190, Folder 19)
  - The Master of Blacktower
    - Author's proof, 25 February 1966 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Serialisation in Femmes d'Aujourd'hui, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Draft - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 38, Folder 12-13)
    - Draft - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 38, Folder 14-15)
    - Cover proof, undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Reviews, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Plot outlines and notes, undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Sons of the Wolf
    - First draft - annotated typescript, 1967; 2 Folders (Box 38, Folder 19-20)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Plot outlines and notes, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Prince of Darkness
    - Page proofs, undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - First draft - annotated typescript, December 1968 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Second revision - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 38, Folder 25-26)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1969? (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Plot outlines and notes, 1968? (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - The Dark on the Other Side
    - Galleys, 20 July 1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Rough draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
    - Revised draft - typescript, March 1970; 2 Folders (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
    - Setting copy - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
    - Galley proofs, 25 August 1970 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Plot outline and notes, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - "False start #1", undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Cover proofs and layout sketches, 1970? (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Cosmopolitan - serialization, November 1970 (Box 190, Folder 20)
  - The Crying Child
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
    - Setting copy - annotated typescript, February 1971; 2 Folders (Box 39, Folder 15-16)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Plot outlines and notes, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Greygallows
    - Setting copy - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 39, Folder 19-20)
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 39, Folder 21-22)
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
    - Plot outlines, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Cover proof, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1972-1993 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Notes, undated (Box 191, Folder 25)
  - Witch
    - Setting copy - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 40, Folder 6-7)
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
    - Revised draft - typescript, March 1973; 2 Folders (Box 40, Folder 10-11)
    - Plot outline, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - House of Many Shadows
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 40, Folder 14-15)
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 40, Folder 16-17)
    - Plot outlines and notes, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Cover proof, undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - The Sea King's Daughter
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 40, Folder 21-22)
    - Draft - annotated typescript (folder 1), undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Draft - annotated typescript (folder 2), undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Plot outlines and notes, 1975? (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1977-1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Patriot's Dream
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 41, Folder 5-7)
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 41, Folder 8-10)
    - Plot outlines and notes, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Cover proof, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Wings of the Falcon
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 41, Folder 16-17)
    - Plot outline and notes, undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Cover proof, undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1978-1995 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Intimita - serialization (folders 1-3), 1983-1984; 3 Folders (Box 190, Folders 21-23)
    - Intimita - serialization (folder 4), 1983-1984 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Wait for What Will Come
    - Galley proofs, undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 41, Folder 22-23)
    - Revised draft - typescript (folder 1), undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Revised draft - typescript (folder 2), undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Plot outline and notes, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1978-1990 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - The Walker in Shadows
    - Second pass - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
    - First pass - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 42, Folder 6-7)
    - First draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 42, Folder 10-11)
    - Revised draft - annotated typescript (copy), undated; 2 Folders (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
    - Carbon copy - typescript, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Page layouts and sketches, 1979; 2 Folders (Box 42, Folder 15-16)
    - Bound page proofs, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Plot outlines and notes, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1981? (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - The Wizard's Daughter
    - Draft - annotated typescript (folder 1), undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Draft - annotated typescript (folders 2-3), undated; 2 Folders (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 43, Folder 3-5)
    - Plot outline and notes, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1980-2000 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Here I Stay
    - Rough draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 43, Folder 8-10)
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Plot outlines and notes, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1983-1985 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Cover proof, undated (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - The Grey Beginning
    - Rough draft - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 43, Folder 15-16)
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Publicity and reviews, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Plot outline, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Be Buried in the Rain
    - Author's proof, undated; 2 Folders (Box 43, Folder 21-22)
    - Setter's proof - annotated typescript (folder 1), undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Setter's proof - annotated typescript (folders 2-3), undated; 2 Folders (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
    - Galley proofs, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 44, Folder 4-6)
    - Revised draft - typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 44, Folder 7-8)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Plot outlines, notes, and style sheet, 1984? (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Search the Shadows
    - Setter's proof - annotated typescript, 1989?; 4 Folders (Box 44, Folder 11-14)
    - Rough draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 44, Folder 15-17)
    - Revised draft - typescript (folders 1-2), undated; 2 Folders (Box 44, Folder 18-19)
    - Revised draft - typescript (folder 3), undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - First draft - annotated typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Revisions, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Smoke and Mirrors
    - Draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 45, Folder 6-8)
    - First pass - annotated typescript, 1989?; 4 Folders (Box 45, Folder 9-12)
    - First draft - annotated typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Plot outlines, notes, and research materials, 1988? (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Into the Darkness
    - First pass - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 45, Folder 17-19)
    - Second draft - annotated typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
    - Third draft - typescript, undated; 3 Folders (Box 46, Folder 4-6)
    - First draft and inserts - annotated typescript, undated; 2 Folders (Box 46, Folder 7-8)
    - Cover proofs, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Reviews and publicity, 1990-1991? (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Plot outline and notes, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Vanish With the Rose